Guide to the Eldon Dedini Papers
The Ohio State University Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum
- Series IV. Advertising Illustrations, 1980s-2003, Undated
  - Broccoli Invoices to Dave Stidolph at Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 4)
  - Mann Packing, Small Ads, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 5)
  - Old Del Monte, Logos and Ads, 1986 (Box ED 13, Folder 1)
  - Lifetree Software, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Business Review, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 3)
  - Lifetree- People Studies, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 4)
  - Absolut Vodka, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 5)
  - Di Rona Prints (3 Folders), Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 6-8)
  - Sweet Potato Box Final Finishes, November 2000 (Box ED 13, Folder 9)
  - Clam Chowder, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 10)
  - Sue Dewar "Den", 2003 (Box ED 13, Folder 11)
  - Valen Advertising: Visa The 2000 Story, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 12)
  - Concourse d' Elegance Programs, Entry forms, Pulse, 1960s-1970s (Box ED 13, Folder 13)
  - Casa Munras, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 14)
  - Dow Poster Proofs, Undated (Box ED 13, Folder 15)
  - Model Sheets-Broccoli Man, Broccoli Wokly, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 1)
  - Concours D'Elegance poster files, Undated (Box ED 91, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Fresh Produce Processors (NAFPP) Convention, Mann Packing Co., May 15-18, 1991 (Box ED 14, Folder 2)
  - Concours D'Elegance Posters, Undated (Box ED 95, Folder 10)
  - Mann Rodeo, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 3)
  - Mann Packing Lettuce: Shredded, Chopped-Salad Mix, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 4)
  - Mann Packing/Broccoli Wokly Photo Collage-Harry Sunshine, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 5)
  - Mann Packing Nature Vac, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 6)
  - Mann Packing Salad Mix-Chopped-Shredded, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 7)
  - Mann Packing Co.-Green Brick Road-Hearts of Broccoli, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 8)
  - NAFPP Convention, Orlando, 1993 (Box ED 14, Folder 9)
  - Broccoli First Roughs for Stidolph- Originals, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 10)
  - Mann Packing, Ethnic Corrections Poster, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 11)
  - Mann Packing, half page ads, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 12)
  - Lettuce-Mann Packing-Broccoli-Lorri Nucci Logos, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 13)
  - Broccoli Wokly Two-Step, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 14)
  - Mann Packing, Halloween Place Mat Broccoli Wokly Figure Insert, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 15)
  - Mann Packing Co., Idaho Potato Poster, Undated (Box ED 14, Folder 16)
  - Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 15, Folder 1)
  - Mann Packing, Early, Undated (Box ED 15, Folder 2)
  - Mann Batista Moon, Undated (Box ED 15, Folder 3)
  - Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 15, Folder 4)
  - Mann Packing Lettuce, Undated (Box ED 15, Folder 5)
  - NAFPP Convention Palm Desert, 1993 (Box ED 15, Folder 6)
  - Inside the Prep Room, Broccoli Wokly, Drummer Boy/Color and Line Black and White, Undated (Box ED 15, Folder 7)
  - NAFPP Convention Colorado, 1992 (Box ED 15, Folder 8)
  - Mann Packing, Pam Musgrave, Black and White Kids, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 3)
  - Poster, Idaho Potato for Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 5)
  - Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 6)
  - Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 7)
  - Mann Packing 2 Page Ads 2 Classics Car-Broccoli Wokly, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 4)
  - Mann Packing Iceberg Lettuce, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 1)
  - Mann Packing, Undated (Box ED 16, Folder 2)
  - Mann Packing Co. Inc. The Adventures of Broccoli Wokly, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 1)
  - Mann Packing Co. Old-Fashioned Green Grocer, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 2)
  - Mann Packing Co. half Page Ad Cole Slaw Mt., Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 3)
  - Pinocchio for Mann Packing Company, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 4)
  - Mann Packing 2 Classics-Franklin Mint Car: Photo and Broccoli Wokly, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 5)
  - D. Stidolph Mann Broccoli, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 6)
  - Mann Packing "Thank you, Mr. President...", Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 7)
  - Broccoli Festival Greenfield-Mann Packing Co., Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 8)
  - "Beginner's Book of Nutrition" Dave Stidolph, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 9)
  - Sunny Shores Cauli Verde, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 10)
  - Mann Packing Sunny Shores Kids Grocery Counters, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 11)
  - Mann Packing Broccoli Hearts Box Design Final Version, Undated (Box ED 17, Folder 12)
  - Roughs for Broccoli Wokly "Listen and Learn" Cassette, Undated (Box ED 18, Folder 1)
  - Broccoli Wokly Man Fantasy Situations, Undated (Box ED 18, Folder 2)
  - Camp Broccoli Wokly Menu Madness, Undated (Box ED 18, Folder 3)
  - Mann Packing half page ads, Picnic on the Grass/4 Chefs-salads-lobster, Undated (Box ED 18, Folder 4)
  - Mann's Hearts of Broccoli Box Design People, Undated (Box ED 18, Folder 5)
  - Broccoli Wokly man, broccoli roughs, Undated (Box ED 18, Folder 6)
  - Mann Packing Co. Inc./Idaho Potato Poster, Undated (Box ED 111, Folder 4)
  - Stu Heinecke/Comedy Advertising, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 6)
  - Stu Heinecke and Partners, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 7)
  - Nutritional All-Stars Preliminary Sketches, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 1)
  - Nutritional All-Star Roughs, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 2)
  - Sweet Potato Rock, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 3)
  - Poster Radionics, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 4)
  - Lifetree Software, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 5)
  - Brooks Firestone, Non-Alcoholic Beer, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 6)
  - Broccoli Wokly, Undated (Box ED 19, Folder 7)
  - Carrot and Broccoli Wokly Coloring Book, Undated (Box ED 20, Folder 1)
  - Stu Heinicke, Project X Mystery Book Club, Undated (Box ED 20, Folder 2)
  - Credit Card Job- Stu Heinicke; Roughs- doctors and lawyers, January 1991 (Box ED 20, Folder 3)
  - Stu Heinicke Comedy Adv. Prints, 1990s (Box ED 20, Folder 4)
  - Father Lueck, Undated (Box ED 33, Folder 4)
  - Eurocard, 1981 (Box ED 93, Folder 13)
  - Mann Packing Broccoli Wokly Ads and Clippings, 1990s (Box ED 93, Folder 14)
  - Mann Packing Advertisements, 1980-190s (Box ED 93, Folder 15)
  - TM Marketing Project, 1989 (Box ED 93, Folder 16)
  - Proofs from Advertising Age; Chicago Tribune Campaign, 1959 (Box ED 94, Folder 1)
  - Proofs from Audi Advertisement, 1986 (Box ED 95, Folder 1)
  - Proof from The Warehouse restaurant Advertisement, Undated (Box ED 95, Folder 2)
  - Mann's Packing Advertising, 1990s (Box ED 95, Folder 3)
  - Talbott Ties Golfers Tearsheets, 1970s (Box ED 95, Folder 4)
  - Old Del Monte Golfers Tearsheets, 1970s-1990s (Box ED 95, Folder 5)
  - Mann's Packing Broccoli Wokly Boxes, Undated (Map-case AC.AH6.001)
  - Mann's Packing Broccoli Wokly Florettes Boxes, Undated (Map-case AC.AH6.002)
  - Mann's Packing Hearts of Broccoli Boxes, Undated (Map-case AC.AH6.003)
- Series V. Book Illustrations, Undated
  This series contains the work that Dedini did for various book illustrations. Of significant note is the work he did for the Microsoft book: A much, much better world. Although many materials in the series are undated it is presumed they were created throughout Dedini's career, 1940s-2000s.
  - Hellelujah, Ernest Ellies, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 8)
  - Monks, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 9)
  - Girl Watchers, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 10)
  - Nadia, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 11)
  - Deadlines, Doxies, and Demagogues (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 12-13)
  - Noah's Ark by Ephraim Kishon, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 14)
  - The Trouble with Heaven, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 15)
  - Zoomar, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 16)
  - The Grass Lovers, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 17)
  - Potatoes are Cheaper, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 18)
  - More Caviar, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 19)
  - Bomb in Attic, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 20)
  - Sleep Til Noon, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 21)
  - Barefoot Boy with Cheek, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 22)
  - Feather Merchants, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 23)
  - The Many Loves of Doby Gillis, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 24)
  - Eternal Bliss Machine, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 25)
  - Gift from the Boys, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 26)
  - Gather No Moss, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 27)
  - Operation Elvis, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 28)
  - Rally Round the Flag Boys, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 26)
  - John Downing, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 30)
  - Ina H., Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 31)
  - Pomp and Circumstances (Noel Coward), Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 32)
  - Arthur Rankin Jr., "Satyrs and Nymphs", Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 33)
  - Tevis, Richard (The Miracle at San Juan), Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 33)
  - Padre, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 34)
  - Brochure for All Saints Cookbook, 1986 (Box ED 12, Folder 35)
  - Brother Larry Cookbook, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 36)
  - Cookbook Bookkeeping, 1980s (Box ED 12, Folder 37)
  - Cookbook Prints, "The Portly Padre or Brother Larry in the Kitchen", Undated (Box ED 3, Folder 13)
  - Monks, etc., Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 39)
  - Brother Larry Prints, Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 40)
  - Logo-etc. and Portly Padre Cookbook, 1980s (Box ED 12, Folder 42)
  - Saints (drawings of), Undated (Box ED 12, Folder 43)
  - The Passionate Invaders, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 1)
  - Chaplain's Raid, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 2)
  - Love Me, Love My Wife, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 3)
  - RCA, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 4)
  - Anyone Got a Match?, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 5)
  - I Was a Teenage Dwarf, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 6)
  - Sam Gross Royalties, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 7)
  - S. Gross Xmas, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 8)
  - Sam Gross Movies, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 9)
  - Sam Gross Gags, Books, Etc., Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 10)
  - Sam Gross Cat Calendar, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 11)
  - S. Gross-Mothers, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 12)
  - Sam Gross Lawyer Joke Book, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 13)
  - Sam Gross Food, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 14)
  - Bill McIntyre, roughs from The Sexperts and The Sexperts Ride Again, 1970s-1980s (Box ED 21, Folder 15)
  - If You Have a Lemon, Make Lemonade, 1975 (Box ED 21, Folder 16)
  - Written Titles and Captions for Dedini Gallery, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 17)
  - Yvette (language textbook illustration), Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 18)
  - La Clef Cover; contract/correspondence on book (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 19-20)
  - Microsoft Book, Early Further Proofs (final), Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 21)
  - Microsoft Book, Semi-Final Proofs, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 22)
  - Microsoft Book, Final Xeroxes, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 23)
  - Microsoft Book, Dedini notes for Vol. 2; plus last sent, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 24)
  - Okayed Roughs for Microsoft Book; first group and second group, (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 25-26)
  - Microsoft Book, Special chapters not used, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 27)
  - Microsoft Book, Finished Okayed, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 28)
  - Notes in the Works, Microsoft Book, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 29)
  - Microsoft Book Duplicates, Finished Xeroxes, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 30)
  - Microsoft Book Project, Bookkeeping, Undated (Box ED 21, Folder 31)
  - State Theatre Posters, Gloria & Ted Gargiulo, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 1)
  - Girl Watchers Guide, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 2)
  - Good-bye Ophelia, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 3)
  - Tracings of A Much, Much Better World, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 4)
  - Buzz Rainer, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 5-6)
  - Deborah Smith, 101 Carnel Nights, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 7)
  - A Much, Much, Better World, Computer/Special Chapters Not Used, Large Size Idea Sketches, Undated (Box ED 22, Folder 8)
  - Adultery for Adults roughs (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 17-18)
  - Computer Sketches, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 19)
  - Whitehead-Microsoft/Correspondence-Microsoft Press, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 20)
  - Oliver Poster, performed at All- Saints Day School, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 1)
  - Ina Hillebrandt, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 2)
  - Dedini Gallery and Grass Lovers, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 3)
  - Roughs for paperbacks, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 4)
  - Collection of Lenin Quotes for Possible Book, Undated (Box ED 93, Folder 17)
  - Reviews of The Dedini Gallery, 1960s (Box ED 93, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with Editor, Contract and Details for The Dedini Gallery, 1960s (Box ED 93, Folder 19)
  - You Are Who You Eat: The Revolutionary New Cannibal Diet, Book Project, 1998 (Box ED 93, Folder 20)
  - Drawings for Archie's 50th Anniversary Book, 1991 (Box ED 95, Folder 6)
  - The Portly Padre or Brother Larry in the Kitchen, Paste-up Book and Proof Illustrations, 1980s (Box ED 95, Folder 7)
  - Photostats of School Book, Children's Book, Undated (Box ED 95, Folder 8)
- Series VI. Freelance Works, 1940-2005
  This series contains freelance work that Dedini created. He was largely involved with his church and produced a number of works for them for various functions.
  - 50 year Reunion Poster Xeroxes, Igor Kipnis (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 6-7)
  - Proofs of Braverman and Merry Go Round, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 9)
  - Carmel Music Society- Leontyne Price, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Ahlgren Logos, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 22)
  - Adventures in Dining, tracing and roughs, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 22)
  - Bauhaus Pictures, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 23)
  - Adobe Tour, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 24)
  - Ibsen (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 25-26)
  - Adventures in Dining, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 27)
  - Food Ideas, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 28)
  - Modern Maturity Magazine, roughs to Michelle Urry, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 29)
  - Gags done for Microsoft, Business Gags, Misc., Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 30)
  - Harvard Business Review, Undated (Box ED 23, Folder 31)
  - Golf Characters, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 5)
  - Quinado Wines, Undated (Box ED 24, Folder 8)
  - Monterey Life Magazine Cover notes and tracings, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 1)
  - Tony Secunda, Correspondence and Contract (4 Folders), 1990-1992 (Box ED 25, Folder 2-5)
  - Sam Morse (Bicycle Classic), Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 6)
  - Walk Walk Walk Club, 2001-2002 (Box ED 25, Folder 7)
  - Look Magazine Correspondence with Gurney Williams and Jack Flagler, 1960s-1970s (Box ED 25, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy Associates, 1960s (Box ED 25, Folder 9)
  - Erik Simonsen, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 10)
  - Early Check Reprints Records, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 11)
  - Snoeck, Ducajli, and Zoon, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 12)
  - Carte Blanche Magazine, 1969-1970 (Box ED 25, Folder 13)
  - Gag Writer- Ben Cassell and Norma A. Van Gochros, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 14)
  - Western's World Gag Notes, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 15)
  - Medical Economics, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 16)
  - True Magazine, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 17)
  - Peter Rauch, Money Magazine, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 18)
  - Bach Festival, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 19)
  - Sabin-McEwen, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 20)
  - The Washingtonian, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 21)
  - Nellie Cards, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 22)
  - Holiday, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 23)
  - Logo, Festival Theatre of California, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 24)
  - Nadya, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 25)
  - Casa Munras, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 26)
  - Ugrudz, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 27)
  - Microsoft Special, not used in A Much, Much Better World book project, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 28)
  - Microsoft Corp. Royalty Statements, 1986-1990 (Box ED 25, Folder 29)
  - Solvang, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 30)
  - Hidden Valley Music Seminars, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 31)
  - Logo for Festival Theatre of California (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 32-33)
  - Sports Illustrated Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 34)
  - Dell- Bill McIntyre, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 35)
  - Carmel Art Auction- Stephanie, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 36)
  - Monterey Research Park- Musgrove (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 37-38)
  - Punch, Undated (Box ED 25, Folder 39)
  - Sales Ledgers for Captions (36 Volumes), 1947-2005 (Box ED 26, Folder 1-36)
  - Roger Fremier- The Photographic Center (3 Folders), Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Capsules, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 4)
  - Crispo, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 5)
  - Lifetree, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 6)
  - Sam Gross, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 7)
  - Lifetree, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 8)
  - Early Gags (3 Folders), 1950s-1960s (Box ED 27, Folder 9-11)
  - Gags, 1969-1972 (Box ED 27, Folder 12)
  - Gags, 1971 (Box ED 27, Folder 13)
  - Gags, ca.1973 (Box ED 27, Folder 14)
  - Early Saved Roughs, 1970-1980 (Box ED 27, Folder 15)
  - Gags, 1983-1985 (Box ED 27, Folder 16)
  - Gags (5 Folders), Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 17-21)
  - Private Bath (A panel cartoon done for the Salinas Index-Journal and Salinas Morning Post 1940-41, done when Fort Ord was re-activated for WWII), 1940-1941 (Box ED 27, Folder 22)
  - Travel, Western's World, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 23)
  - Quinado Wines, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 24)
  - Mission Bell-Brother Larry roughs, xeroxes, tearsheets, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 25)
  - Kennedy Associates, Roughs, and Correspondence about Freelance Work, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 26)
  - Xeroxes-Printed Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 27, Folder 27)
  - Gross Income, 1955 (Box ED 27, Folder 28)
  - Gross Income, 1960 (Box ED 27, Folder 29)
  - Long Beach Drummers; for nephew, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 1)
  - Davi Political Posters, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 2)
  - D'Angelo Lake Tahoe, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 3)
  - Leotyne Price, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 4)
  - Mozart, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 5)
  - Crosby Golf, Special Projects, Misc. Xeroxes, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 6)
  - First Night, Susan Britton, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 7)
  - April Fest Alzheimer's, 1986 (Box ED 28, Folder 8)
  - Peter Hay, Pebble Beach Golf Logo, 1992 (Box ED 28, Folder 9)
  - Grove-Portola Savings, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 10)
  - Grove-Portola Photo Stats, Undated (Box ED 28, Folder 11)
  - Quinado Wines, Undated (Box ED 29, Folder 1)
  - Roger Payner Senator Poster, Undated (Box ED 29, Folder 2)
  - Xeroxes of Assorted Works, 2000 (Box ED 29, Folder 3)
  - Xeroxes of Assorted Works, 2001 (Box ED 29, Folder 4)
  - Xeroxes of Assorted Works, 1997-1999 (Box ED 29, Folder 5)
  - It's About Love- Harrison Memorial Library, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 1)
  - All Saints Logo (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 2-3)
  - Santa Inez Classic, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 4)
  - First U.S. Post Office Monterey, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 5)
  - All Saints Rummage Sale, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 6)
  - All Saints Book Fair, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 7)
  - Bruce Ariss, Maritime Museum Mural, 1991 (Box ED 30, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Conroy Portfolio, Judge Gags, Virginia Conroy Sketch of Eldon Dedini, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 9)
  - Grove- Portola, Undated (Box ED 30, Folder 10)
  - Carmel Mission Posters, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 1)
  - Carmel Mission Fiesta (2 Folders), 1992-1993 (Box ED 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Book Reviews, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 1)
  - "Come Have Coffee with Us", Bye Bye Braverman, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 2)
  - Ledger Sheets/Records of Cartoons Sent and Sold in LA, 1942-1944 (Box ED 31, Folder 3)
  - Records of Cartoons/Gags sold; Remittance slips/invoices from Esquire, New Yorker, etc.; King Features, other, 1947-1954 (Box ED 31, Folder 4)
  - Mission Bell - Cartoons for Church Newsletter, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 5)
  - Fat Jokes/Done for ":Time of Your Life" magazine Frank Hiteshew Assoc., 1972-1973 (Box ED 31, Folder 6)
  - Notes, Old Del Monte and Talbot Ties, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 7)
  - The Warehouse, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 8)
  - Bank of America Commercial Account, Check record/Ledger sheets, 1960-1968 (Box ED 31, Folder 9)
  - Monterey Commercial Bank, 1953-1958 (Box ED 31, Folder 10)
  - Early Studio Receipts, LA years, 1940s-1950s (Box ED 31, Folder 11)
  - Bank of America Commercial Account, LA and Monterey, 1950 (Box ED 31, Folder 12)
  - Monterey Commercial Bank, Check records, 1959-1963 (Box ED 31, Folder 13)
  - Monterey Commercial Bank, 1965-1968 (Box ED 31, Folder 14)
  - Concours d' Elegance Posters, Notes, and Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box ED 31, Folder 15)
  - Concours d' Elegance, Notes and Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box ED 31, Folder 16)
  - Concours d' Elegance, Notes, 1972 (Box ED 31, Folder 17)
  - Concours d' Elegance, First Year, 1966 (Box ED 31, Folder 18)
  - Monterey Life including Dedini, Arriola, and Ketcham article, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 19)
  - Di Rona, Good Scenes, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 20)
  - Di Rona, Possible?, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 21)
  - Di Rona, Gag Roughs, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 22)
  - Concours d' Elegance, Undated (Box ED 31, Folder 23)
  - St. Marks, Undated (Box ED 32, Folder 1)
  - Binsacca, Undated (Box ED 32, Folder 2)
  - Hartnell, Undated (Box ED 32, Folder 3)
  - Making Strides Against Cancer, Undated (Box ED 32, Folder 4)
  - Celebrations 1975, All Saints (Box ED 32, Folder 5)
  - Dedini Caricature for Marc Cohen, 1980s (Box ED 32, Folder 6)
  - Heineman Galleries, September- November 1994 (Box ED 33, Folder 1)
  - Concours, 1990 (Box ED 33, Folder 2)
  - All Saint, Logos, Flyers, Posters, and ketches, Undated (Box ED 33, Folder 3)
  - 75th Anniversary State Theater Poster (Frankenstein, Dracula), 2001 (Box ED 33, Folder 4)
  - Old Del Monte Golf Course, Undated (Box ED 33, Folder 5)
  - Charity Golf Poster, Undated (Box ED 33, Folder 6)
  - Look Magazine (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 1-2)
  - KRML Jazz and Blues, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 3)
  - S. Harris, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 4)
  - Cartoonists Against Drug Abuse, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 5)
  - Julia Child Menu, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 6)
  - Monterey Blues Festival (2 Folders), 2000 (Box ED 34, Folder 7-8)
  - John Steinbeck T-Shirt Design, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 9)
  - Brother Larry, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 10)
  - Peter Heller, Undated (Box ED 34, Folder 11)
  - Carmel Graphics, Undated (Box ED 35, Folder 1)
  - Festival Logo, Undated (Box ED 35, Folder 2)
  - Bruce Ariss, Undated (Box ED 35, Folder 3)
  - David Loye, Undated (Box ED 35, Folder 4)
  - Oleg Kobalenko, Undated (Box ED 36, Folder 1)
  - Di Rona Portfolio, Undated (Box ED 36, Folder 2)
  - Local Political Cartoons by Dedini, ca. 1965 (Box ED 36, Folder 3)
  - Payment Schedule, 2002-2004 (Box ED 93, Folder 21)
  - Magazines, 2000s (Box ED 93, Folder 22)
  - Receipts of Cartoons Sold, 1957 (Box ED 93, Folder 23)
  - Gross Income Receipts, 1958 (Box ED 93, Folder 24)
  - Disney Clippings, 1944-1980s (Box ED 93, Folder 25)
    Includes Employee ID Card
  - "A Shooting Script" Notes and Drafts, Undated (Box ED 93, Folder 26)
  - Bath Pillow Illustrations, 1992 (Box ED 93, Folder 27)
  - Proposal for TV Series "You Are Who You Eat" Hillebrandt Consultants, 1998 (Box ED 93, Folder 28)
  - Proofs and Tearsheets from True, Look, and Other Publications, 1940s-1980s (Box ED 93, Folder 29)
  - Assorted Freelance Works, Undated (Box ED 93, Folder 30)
  - Transparencies, "The Salinas That Used to be!", ca.1940-1942 (Box ED 94, Folder 2)
  - Tearsheets of Drawings for the Salinas Index-Journal and Salinas Morning Post, 1940-1942 (Box ED 94, Folder 3)
  - Nut Management, Roughs and Copies, Undated (Box ED 95, Folder 8)
  - Transparency of Internal Revenue Service Cartoon, Undated (Box ED 95, Folder 9)
  - Covers of "300" For Bowlers, 1943 (Box ED 96, Folder 1)
  - Flora's Monterey Tearsheet, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 2)
  - Proofs, Tearsheets, and Clippings of Dedini Illustrations, Undated (Box ED 97, Folder 1)
  - Proofs from Assorted Freelance Projects, Undated (Box ED 97, Folder 2)
  - Tearsheets, Proofs, Clippings of Illustration for Monterey Area Events, 1950s-2000s (Box ED 97, Folder 3)
- Series VII. Roughs, Sketches, and Drawings, 1950-2005